Sakshi Sakshi

Meerut, Uttar Pradesh sakshichaudhary855@gmail.com 9003205425

Solution-driven professional excelling in highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions to challenges and focused on customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused apps using react native and JavaScript. Experience building products for mobile app users, meeting highest standards for app design, user experience, best practices, usability and speed. Responding to challenges by designing and developing solutions and building mobile applications aligned to customer's services. Translating solutions into code and working across many different APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Front End Developer

TCS - Noida, Uttar Pradesh September 2018 to Present

Created eye catching and functional digital design concepts using react native platform to strengthen company brand and identity.

Used various concepts like redux, reduxSaga and other react native libraries to build mobile applications

Took concepts and produced design mockups and prototypes to strengthen designs, enhance user experiences and improve app interactions.

Created layouts and user interface using react native elements.

Inter Trainee

DRDO - Dehra Dun, Uttarakhand June 2017 to July 2017

Received training and certification from DRDO and learned about various concepts of thermal imaging and its implementation in defence sector.

PROFESSIONAL React Native

Education

B.tech in ECE

SRM Institute Of Science - Chennai, Tamil Nadu July 2014 to May 2018

Skills / IT Skills

- Javascript (2 years)
- React (2 years)
- React Native (2 years)
- Css (2 years)
- Html (2 years)
- Redux (2 years)
- ReduxSaga (2 years)
- D3.js (1 year)

Online Profile

https://instagram.com/sakshi.codes

https://scjuly19.github.io/folio